Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-20. Rules. Pennsylvania Railroad Company
    - Assistant Movement Directors, 1940-1948 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - General, 1963 (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1952-1956 (Box 303, Folder 9)
      August 1952-56.
    - General, 1959-1961 (Box 303, Folder 10)
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 303, Folder 11)
    - General, 1962 (Box 303, Folder 12)
      May-December 1962.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1961-1962 (Box 303, Folder 13)
      June 1961-April 1962.
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - 40-Hour Week -1948-1950 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Union Shop, 1955-1962 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6197, 1959-1964 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5507, 1956-1957 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case No. A-7078, 1963-1964 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Union Shop. Court Cases involving Carr, J.P.; Fields, E., et. al.; Higgins, J.J., Jr.; Price, J.H.; White, A., Jr., 1956-1958 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Union Shop. Fields, E., et. al., 1957 (Box 304, Folder 8)
      1957 December 30
    - Case No. 5968. Fagan, H.J., 1957-1960 (Box 304, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1948-1950 (Box 304, Folder 10)
      1948-February 1950.
    - Fagan, H.J., et. al., 1957-1960 (Box 304, Folder 11)
    - Agreement, 1942 (Box 304, Folder 12)
      1942 May 1
    - Union Shop. Fields, E., et. al.; Carr, J.P.; White, A.H., Jr., 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Saltsgiver, E.V., 1955 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Saltsgiver, E.V., 1954-1955 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. 4989, 1955-1956 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1954 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Lodge No. 163, 1953-1954 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Union Shop. Fulwood, A., Sr., 1953-1956 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1947 (Box 305, Folder 8)
      February-December 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1944-1947 (Box 305, Folder 9)
      1944-January 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1942-1943 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1938-1941 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1936-1937 (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1924-1933 (Box 305, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1937-1938 (Box 305, Folder 14)
    - Agreements (Box 305, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1923-1924 (Box 305, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-21. Rules. Great Northern Railroad
    - Supplemental Pension. National Mediation Board Case No. A-7818, 1964-1966 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5934, 1958-1960 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - General, 1957-1962 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5837, 1958-1959 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Rules Movement. Superior, Wisconsin; Seattle, Washington (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Representation. Case No. C-1693, 1947-1958 (Box 306, Folder 7-8)
    - Wages. Mediation Case No. A-6569, 1961-1962 (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Veterans Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1955-1957 (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - Case No. A-1788, 1944-1945 (Box 306, Folder 12)
    - Great Northern Railroad, 1949-1956 (Box 306, Folder 13)
      November 1949-56.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 306, Folder 14)
    - 279-21 (a). General, 1947-1949 (Box 306, Folder 15)
      December 1947-October 1949.
    - 279-21 (a). Great Northern Railroad, 1946-1947 (Box 306, Folder 16)
      1946-November 1947.
    - 279-21 (a). Great Northern Railroad, 1944-1945 (Box 306, Folder 17)
    - 279-21 (b-Section 2). Rules Revision. Case No. A-946, 1942-1946 (Box 306, Folder 18)
    - Welfare Benefits, 1951-1955 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Concession Department, King Street Station, 1952 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Teletype, 1948-1953 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Hours, 1944 (Box 307, Folder 5)
      1944 December 1
    - 279-21 (b- Section 1). Rules Revision. Case No. A-946 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - 279-21 (a). Great Northern Railroad, 1926-1939 (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Case No. A-946, 1940-1941 (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - 279-21 (a). Great Northern Railroad, 1940-1943 (Box 307, Folder 9)
    - Case No. A-1442, 1943-1944 (Box 307, Folder 10)
    - Great Northern Railroad, 1921-1929 (Box 307, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-22. Rules. Northern Pacific Railway Company
    - Agreements, 1946 (Box 307, Folder 12)
    - Tie Plants. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 307, Folder 13)
    - Ore Docks. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 307, Folder 14)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 307, Folder 15)
    - 279-22 (a). Ore Dock Employees, 1944 (Box 307, Folder 16)
    - 279-22 (b). Merchandise Docks at Duluth, Minnesota, 1937-1943 (Box 307, Folder 17)
    - 279-22 (c). Timber Treating Plants, 1939-1943 (Box 307, Folder 18)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 307, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 307, Folder 20)
    - Ore Docks, Superior, Wisconsin. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 307, Folder 21)
    - Timber Preservation Plants, Brainerd, Minnesota; Paradise, Montana. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 307, Folder 22)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1958 (Box 307, Folder 23)
    - Veterans Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1955-1957 (Box 307, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-23. Rules. Texas and Pacific Railway Company
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Case No. R-1642, 1946-1947 (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Case No. R-1642, 1946 (Box 308, Folder 3)
      1946 September 16
    - Arbitration, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 4-7)
      1945 October 16
    - Rules Revision, 1943-1944 (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - 279-23 (Section 2). Case No. A-1801, 1945-1946 (Box 308, Folder 9)
      September 1945-46.
    - 279-23 (Section 1). Case No. A-1801, 1944-1945 (Box 308, Folder 10)
      1944-August 1945.
    - Case No. A-1801. Exhibits, 1934-1945 (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - Arbitration, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 12-14)
      September 17, 1945-October 15, 1945.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 308, Folder 15)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6397, 1956-1961 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6396, 1959-1961 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6241, 1960-1962 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6313, 1960-1961 (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - General, 1956-1962 (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - General, 1948-1955 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Agreement, 1940 (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1945-1947 (Box 309, Folder 10)
      November 1945-47.
    - Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1934-1945 (Box 309, Folder 11)
      1934-October 1945.
    - Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1944 (Box 309, Folder 12)
      1944 August 2
    - Case No. C-623, 1931-1933 (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - Cases Nos. C-562, C-622, C-623, 1930-1932 (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1923-1929 (Box 309, Folder 15)
    - Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 309, Folder 16)
    - Union Shop, 1953-1956 (Box 310, Folder 1)
      July 1953-56.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-24. Rules. Soo Line Railroad Company
    - General, 1956-1961 (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Soo Line Railroad Company, 1951-1955 (Box 310, Folder 4)
      March 1951-55.
    - Supplemental Agreement, 1950 (Box 310, Folder 5)
      1950 September 1
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Case No. A-4219, 1952-1953 (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - Soo Line Railroad Company, 1947-1951 (Box 310, Folder 8)
      1947-February 1951.
    - Ore Dock. 40-Hour Week, 1949-1951 (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - Vacation Dispute. Stolz, T.M., 1949-1950 (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Teletype, 1948-1949 (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Case No. A-1844, 1944-1946 (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Soo Line Railroad Company, 1944-1946 (Box 310, Folder 15)
    - Soo Line Railroad Company, 1932-1939 (Box 310, Folder 16)
    - Soo Line Railroad Company, 1940-1943 (Box 310, Folder 17)
    - Soo Line Railroad Company, 1921-1929 (Box 310, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-25. Rules. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company
    - 279-25 (Section 2). Mediation Case No. A-6535, 1959-1961 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - 279-25 (Section 1). Mediation Case No. A-6535, 1959-1961 (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6280, 1956-1961 (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Joint Notice, 1958 (Box 311, Folder 4)
      1958 May 27
    - Abolition of Position No. 7659, Montrose, Missouri, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1955-1957 (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Abolition of Position No. 6604, Lockhart, Texas, 1956 (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - 279-25 (Section 3). 40-Hour Week, 1925-1953 (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - 279-25 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1949 (Box 311, Folder 9)
      July 25, 1949-September 15, 1949.
    - 279-25 (Section 1). 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 311, Folder 10)
      1948-July 26, 1949.
    - United States Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 311, Folder 11)
      1921 June, 25
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company, 1921-1922 (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Case No. A-790. Exhibits, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - Panel Board Hearing, 1945 (Box 312, Folder 1)
      January 24-29, 1945.
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Case No. A-790, 1940-1945 (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 312, Folder 4)
      1951-March 1953.
    - Mediation Case No. A-5587, 1957-1959 (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - General, 1952-1956 (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company, 1947-1951 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Movement of Offices, 1957 (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - General, 1945-1946 (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - General, 1940-1944 (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Revenue Computerization, Chesapeake District, 1958 (Box 312, Folder 12)
      1958 September 19
  - Sub-Series 279-26. Rules. Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - General, 1952-1955 (Box 313, Folder 2)
      October 1952-55.
    - General, 1950-1952 (Box 313, Folder 3)
      October 1950-September 1952.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1947-1950 (Box 313, Folder 4)
      1947-September 1950.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1957 (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1945-1946 (Box 313, Folder 6)
      1945-June 1946.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1946 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - 279-26 (a). Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1938-1944 (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - 279-26 (b). Case No. R-875, 1941-1942 (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - 279-26 (b2). Representation Dispute, 1942 (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Agreements, 1946 (Box 313, Folder 11-14)
    - Company Brief. United States Court of Appeals, Sixth Circuit, 1937 (Box 313, Folder 15-17)
      1937 May 29
    - Brotherhood Brief. United States Court of Appeals, Sixth Circuit, 1937 (Box 313, Folder 18-20)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1936-1937 (Box 313, Folder 21)
    - Transcript, United States Court of Appeals, Sixth Circuit, 1936 (Box 314, Folder 1)
      1936 October 7
    - Cases Nos. C-921 and R-62, 1934-1935 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Vacations, 1943-1950 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Case No. R-1509, 1945 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Case No. R-1509. Payroll Record and Eligible Lists, 1945 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Red Caps, 1942-1943 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Case No. R-1509, 1945-1946 (Box 314, Folder 8)
      December 1945-January 21, 1946.
    - Case No. R-1509, 1945 (Box 314, Folder 9)
      July-November 1945.
    - Representation Dispute, 1942 (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - 279-26 (c). Agreement Proposal, Miscellaneous Forces and Red Caps, 1942-1944 (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Agreements, 1946 (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1923 (Box 314, Folder 13)
      February-December 1923.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 314, Folder 14)
      May 1921-February 1922.
    - Exhibits, 1934 (Box 314, Folder 15)
    - Briefs, 1934 (Box 314, Folder 16)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway Company, 1921-1923 (Box 314, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-27. Rules. St. Louis Southwestern Railway
    - Case No. A-3069, 1949-1952 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - 40-Hour Week. Excepted Positions, 1949-1950 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1946-1948 (Box 315, Folder 4)
      October 1946-48.
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1945-1946 (Box 315, Folder 5)
      1945-September 1946.
    - Exhibit No. 13. Revenue Computerization, Chesapeake District, 1958 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Rules Revision. Mediation Case No. C-3578, 1958-1965 (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5142 (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1955 (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - General, 1957-1962 (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - General, 1949-1951 (Box 315, Folder 13)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1952-1956 (Box 315, Folder 14)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1941-1944 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1921-1940 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Agreement (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Excepted Positions. Case No. A-708, 1939-1940 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railway, 1921 (Box 316, Folder 5-6)
  - Sub-Series 279-28. Rules. Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company
    - Mediation Case No. A-6887, 1963-1965 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6833, 1962-1965 (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Mediation Cases Nos. A-4516 and A-2651. Teletype Machines, 1947-1958 (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Case No. A-2652, 1948-1952 (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - UNIVAC, 1955-1956 (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Cases Nos. C-2328 and R-3061, 1954-1956 (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - 1936-1939 (Box 316, Folder 13)
    - February 1934-1935 (Box 316, Folder 14)
    - 1947-February 1949 (Box 316, Folder 15)
    - 279-28 (a). Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1944-1946 (Box 316, Folder 16)
    - 279-28 (a). Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1940-1943 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - March 1949-September 1950 (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949 (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - General, 1952-1953 (Box 317, Folder 4)
      June 1952-53.
    - General, 1950-1952 (Box 317, Folder 5)
      October 1950-May 1952.
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 317, Folder 6)
      1954-May 1955.
    - General, 1957 (Box 317, Folder 7)
      July-December 1957.
    - Exhibit No. 13. Revenue Computerization, Chesapeake District, 1958 (Box 317, Folder 8)
    - Agreements, 1945-1956 (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Case No. A-3945, 1952-1953 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Case No. A-3376, 1950 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1954 (Box 318, Folder 3)
      September 23, 1949-54.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1950 (Box 318, Folder 4)
      1950 August 3
    - Freight Claim and Stationary Department Coordination, 1956 (Box 318, Folder 5)
      April 5, 1956-July 30, 1956.
    - Scope Rule, 1956-1957 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - General -April 1956-February 1957 (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - General -March 1-6, 1957 (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - Agreements, 1957 (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - Reorganization of Operations Accounting, 1955 (Box 318, Folder 10)
      1955 October
    - Payroll Computer Project, 1956 (Box 318, Folder 11)
      1956 January 9
    - General -March 7, 1957-June 1957 (Box 318, Folder 12)
    - Case No. A-3241, 1949 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Vacation Dispute. Cart, I.E., 1948-1949 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - 279-28 (b). Case No. A-623, 1939-1947 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Station Masters, 1945-1947 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Rules Revision, 1944-1945 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Agreement, 1945 (Box 319, Folder 6)
      1945 January 1
    - Proposed Agreement No. 7, 1941 (Box 319, Folder 7-11)
      1941 April 21
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1934-1935 (Box 319, Folder 12)
      1934-35.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1945 (Box 319, Folder 13)
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 319, Folder 14)
      June 1955-March 1956.
    - 279-28 (Section 3). Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1949-1951 (Box 319, Folder 15)
      August 17, 1949-51.
    - 279-28 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1949 (Box 319, Folder 16)
      May 11, 1949-August 16, 1949.
    - 279-28 (Section 1). 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 319, Folder 17)
      1948-May 10, 1949.
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 319, Folder 18)
      1942-50.
    - 279-28 (Section 7). Agreements, 1962-1963 (Box 320, Folder 1)
      December 1962-June 1963.
    - 279-28 (Section 6). Agreements, 1962 (Box 320, Folder 2)
      February 15, 1962-November 1962.
    - 279-28 (Section 5). Agreements, 1961-1962 (Box 320, Folder 3)
      April 20, 1961-February 14, 1962.
    - 279-28 (Section 4). Agreements, 1960-1961 (Box 320, Folder 4)
      1960-April 19, 1961.
    - 279-28 (Section 3). Agreements, 1959 (Box 320, Folder 5)
      December 2-31, 1959.
    - 279-28 (Section 2). Agreements, 1959 (Box 320, Folder 6)
      April 1959-December 1, 1959.
    - 279-28 (Section 1). Agreements, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 7)
      1958-March 1959.
    - General, 1960 (Box 320, Folder 8)
      June-December 1960.
    - Payroll Computer Project, 1959 (Box 320, Folder 9)
      1959 August
    - Coordination of Expenditures Accounting, 1959 (Box 320, Folder 10)
      1959 July
    - Property Accounting Consolidation, 1959 (Box 321, Folder 1)
      1959 March
    - 1958. Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 2)
      1958-59.
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 321, Folder 3)
      July 3, 1959-May 31, 1960.
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 4)
      December 1958-June 30, 1959.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1958 (Box 321, Folder 5)
      1958 November
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1958 (Box 321, Folder 6)
      September-October 1958.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1958 (Box 321, Folder 7)
      January-August 1958.
    - Agreements, 1949-1955 (Box 321, Folder 8)
      1949-55.
    - 279-28 (Section 12). Agreements, 1965 (Box 322, Folder 1)
      August 12, 1965-October 12, 1965.
    - 279-28 (Section 11). Agreements, 1965 (Box 322, Folder 2)
      August 1-11, 1965.
    - 279-28 (Section 10). Agreements, 1965 (Box 322, Folder 3)
      February-July 1965.
    - 279-28 (Section 9). Agreements, 1963-1965 (Box 322, Folder 4)
      December 1963-January 1965.
    - 279-28 (Section 8). Agreements, 1963 (Box 322, Folder 5)
      July-December 1963.
    - General, 1964-1965 (Box 322, Folder 6)
      August 1964-October 1965.
    - General, 1964 (Box 322, Folder 7)
      January-July 1964.
    - General, 1963 (Box 322, Folder 8)
      September 30, 1963-December 1963.
    - General, 1963 (Box 322, Folder 9)
      January 1963-September 29, 1963.
    - General, 1962 (Box 323, Folder 1)
      August 5, 1962-December 1962.
    - General, 1962 (Box 323, Folder 2)
      April 5, 1962-August 4, 1962.
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 323, Folder 3)
      October 1961-April 4, 1962.
    - General, 1961 (Box 323, Folder 4)
      January-September 1961.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 323, Folder 5)
      1951-57.
    - National Labor Relations Board. Dudding, E., 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Health and Welfare, 1953-1957 (Box 323, Folder 7)
      1953-57.
  - Sub-Series 279-29. Rules. Western Pacific Railroad Company
    - 279-29 (Section 3). Rules. Revision. Mediation Case No. A-5869, 1965 (Box 323, Folder 8)
      August-September 1965.
    - 279-29 (Section 2). Rules. Revision. Mediation Case No. A-5869, 1958-1965 (Box 323, Folder 9)
      August 15, 1958-July 1965.
    - 279-29 (Section 1). Rules. Revision. Mediation Case No. A-5869, 1957-1958 (Box 323, Folder 10)
      1957-August 14, 1958.
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 323, Folder 12)
      July 14, 1949-August 10, 1950.
    - Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1949-1951 (Box 323, Folder 13)
      November 1949-February 1951.
    - Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1948-1949 (Box 324, Folder 1)
      1948-August 20, 1949.
    - General, 1956-1962 (Box 324, Folder 2)
      1956-62.
    - Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1952-1955 (Box 324, Folder 3)
      March 1952-55.
    - General, 1951-1952 (Box 324, Folder 4)
      March 1951-February 1952.
    - General, 1946-1949 (Box 324, Folder 5)
      1946-October 1949.
    - General, 1929-1945 (Box 324, Folder 6)
      1929-45.
    - Mediation Case No. A-5033, 1949-1956 (Box 324, Folder 7)
      1949-56.
    - Case No. A-3159, 1949-1952 (Box 324, Folder 8)
      1949-52.
    - Rules. Revision Case No. A-1340, 1939-1944 (Box 324, Folder 9)
      1939-44.
    - Vacation Claim. James, F., 1948 (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Vacation Dispute. Gordon, M.P., 1948 (Box 324, Folder 11)
    - Vacation Dispute. Payment for Overtime, 1945-1948 (Box 324, Folder 12)
      1945-48.
    - Vacation Dispute. Murphy, F., 1946-1947 (Box 324, Folder 13)
      1946-47.
    - Vacation Dispute. McGregor, R., 1946-1947 (Box 324, Folder 14)
    - Vacations, 1942-1946 (Box 324, Folder 15)
      1942-46.
    - Case No. R-1452, 1946-1947 (Box 324, Folder 16)
    - Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1921-1923 (Box 324, Folder 17)
      1921-23.
  - Sub-Series 279-30. Rules. Reading Company
    - General, 1950-1957 (Box 324, Folder 18)
      March 1950-June 1957.
    - Reading Company, 1947-1950 (Box 324, Folder 19)
      October 1947-February 1950.
    - Reading Company, 1946-1947 (Box 324, Folder 20)
      1946-September 1947.
    - Reading Company, 1943-1945 (Box 325, Folder 1)
      1943-45.
    - Reading Company, 1940-1942 (Box 325, Folder 2)
      1940-42.
    - Reading Company, 1935-1939 (Box 325, Folder 3)
      1935-39.
    - Reading Company, 1921-1922 (Box 325, Folder 4)
      1921-22.
    - Vacations, 1942-1946 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      1948-51.
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 325, Folder 7)
      1963-64.
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - Reading Company, 1958-1960 (Box 325, Folder 11)
      1958-August 1960.
    - General, 1964-1965 (Box 325, Folder 12)
      1964-June 1965.
  - Sub-Series 279-31. Rules. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad
    - Union Shop, 1953-1961 (Box 325, Folder 13)
      January 1953-61.
    - General, 1963 (Box 325, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 325, Folder 15)
    - General, 1963 (Box 325, Folder 16)
      January-November 1963.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1958 (Box 326, Folder 1)
      1948-58.
    - General, 1956-1958 (Box 326, Folder 2)
      1956-58.
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 326, Folder 3)
      1959-62.
    - General, 1950-1952 (Box 326, Folder 4)
      March 1950-September 1952.
    - Taylor, J.P.; Taylor, H.; Blake, C., 1952-1959 (Box 326, Folder 5)
      1952-59.
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1952-1955 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - 279-31 (a). General, 1944-1950 (Box 326, Folder 7)
      1944-February 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1952 (Box 326, Folder 8)
      1951-52.
    - Case No. A-3962, 1951-1956 (Box 326, Folder 9)
      1951-56.